年
你就不能放着别玩了吗
Can you just keep it and not play anymore?
年
你就不能放着别玩了吗
Can you just keep it and not play anymore?
不行
No.
解释下那个
Explain that one.
女人总会再给男人一次机会
You always give a guy a second chance.
这算是男人心知肚明的金科玉律
That's, like, the golden rule of guys.
这有什么问题
Then what's the problem?
问题在于我不能让他知道
The problem is I can't let him know
我放任你重蹈覆辙
I'm letting you in the back.
乔安娜  你尽可随意取笑
Look, Joanna, you can go ahead d make fun of this,
但这不是闹着玩的
but this is real important.
我是在向你揭示男人的想法
I mean, I'm telling you what guys think,
如果你想像他们一样  就别乱了规矩
and if you want to be one of the guys, you don't break the code.
抓住男人的命根子不就结了
Held in guy's dick.
这可不轻松
It's no picnic.
不  撒迪厄斯  快走开
No, Thaddeus, go away!
告诉我你的名字
Tell me, what's your name?
泰  泰特
T-Tate.
要是撒迪厄斯再回来吓你
If Thaddeus comes back to scare you again,
就闭上眼  大喊"走开"
just shut your eyes and say, "Go away."
明白了吗  泰特
You understand, Tate?
他不会把你怎样的
He'll mind you
因为我会保护你
'cause I'm going to protect you.
真希望你是我妈妈
I wish you were my mommy.
擦干眼泪  孩子
Now dry your tears, child.
人生苦短  切莫悲伤
Life is too short for so much sorrow.
你是谁
Who are you?
是我  泰特呀
It's me, Tate.
"人生苦短  切莫悲伤"
"Life's too short for so much sorrow."
你错了
You're wrong.
我将永世被困于此
It's an eternity.
日以继夜  无限渴望
Just endless days and nights of longing;
我的孩子在哪儿
where's my baby?
我正是想和你谈谈此事
That's what I want to talk to you about.
你答应过我
You, you promised me.
你会与她生一个  与房子的女主人
You made one with her, the-the lady of the house.
维维安
Vivien.
她是瓦奥莱特的母亲
That's Violet's mother.
我没法再给你那个孩子
And I can't give you that baby anymore.
计划有变  诺拉
Everything's changed, Nora.
我爱上了瓦奥莱特
I'm in love with Violet.
我懂了
I see.
我不能夺走她的亲弟弟
I just can't take her brother away.
但我能
But I can.
我会拿到手的
And I will.
那孩子是我的
That baby is mine.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
翻译：豆丁   Asianika   爱卿溜小鸟   费列罗西瓜   Sakura
时间轴：子衿   加森   搁浅
校对：豆丁   妖月Seraphim
后期：冰河    监制：小豆丁
第一季 第十一集
美国恐怖故事
爸爸  我不是条狗
Dad, I'm not a dog!
我说了我不舒服  把我丢在这就好
I told you I don't feel well! Just leave me here!
不  我再也不相信你了  我也不相信泰特
No, I don't trust you anymore and I don't trust Tate!
泰特  我和他好几周没见面了
Tate? I haven't seen him in weeks!
别再撒谎了  瓦奥莱特  你妈妈就要回家了
No more, Violet. Your mom's coming home
你要和我一起去接她
and you're coming with me to get her.
爸爸  求你了  我不舒服
Dad, please, I don't feel well!
你可以在车里躺着
You can lay down in the car.
等会回家了  就收拾东西
And when you get home, pack up your things.
我们要永远离开这房子
We're leaving this house for good.
什么  你俩又和好了吗
What? You guys are back together?
我还不清楚  你妈妈想
I don't know yet-- your mom wants
去你娇姨妈那分娩  我支持她的想法
to go to Aunt Jo's to give birth, and I'm supporting it.
不  这非你所愿
No, you don't want to do this.
瓦奥莱特  你妈妈被关在
Violet, your mother's been locked up
精神病院好几周了
in a psych ward for weeks.
我不会让她在那里再多待一分钟
I won't let her stay there for another minute.
是你自己上去还是我把你拽上车
Are you gonna get in the car or do I have to make you?
天呐  瓦奥莱特  你到底怎么了
My God, Violet, what is wrong with you?!
上车去  你妈妈想见你
Get in the car! Your mother wants to see you!
我会吐出来的
I'm gonna throw up!
好吧  我躺下就是了
Fine. I'll lay down.
他们回来后会发生什么
What's gonna happen when they get back?
我该说什么
What do I say?
不是UTube  是YouTube
It's not UTube with a U. It's YouTube.
Y-O-U
Y-o-u.
他们若是发现我自杀了
If they find out I killed myself,
会疯掉的
they'll go insane.
这次真心会发疯的
Literally, for real this time.
不能让他们知道
They can't know.
你又不能永远瞒下去
Well, you can't control it forever.
事实摆在眼前  瓦奥莱特
I mean, it is what it is, Violet.
有朝一日  这种电脑会被淘汰
One of these days, this computer will be obsolete.
人们的脑部或是什么地方
People will have microchips implanted
会植入微芯片
in their brains or something.
我们也就没法上YouTube看视频之类的了
We won't be able to watch YouTube or anything.
我们会和其他鬼魂一样
We'll be like all the others here;
困在这个无形的牢房里
prisoners in a windowless cell.
谁能向我展示大千世界的新奇万物
Who's gonna show me the new ways of the world?
这里的鬼魂都不快乐  泰特
Nobody here is happy, Tate.
是的  但咱俩和他们不同
Well, yeah, but they're not like us.
他们孤独寂寞
They're lonely.
我们拥有彼此
We have each other.
我们没法生儿育女
We'll never have kids.
麦德姆没有土豆卖
I was so worried when Madame
我本来还很担心
didn't have any potatoes,
但我得说  红薯刻印的效果更清晰
but I have to say these yams making a cleaner image.
我想是水分更少的缘故
Less moisture, I think.
中国红真好看
I love that Chinese red.
我总想把楼下的盥洗室刷成这颜色
I always meant to use it in the powder room downstairs.
我准备把这旧的婴儿床也刷成这颜色
I'm gonna paint those old cribs, too.
真的吗  大红色的婴儿床
Really? Red cribs?
查德...
Uh, Chad...
我们之前是怎么说的
what did we talk about?
是"咱俩"的孩子  不是"我"的孩子
"Our" babies, not "My" babies.
随你啦  红艳艳的婴儿床又不会死
You know what? I can live with a red crib.
效果或许会超赞呢
It might actually be kind of fabulous.
你开心的样子真迷人
You are so adorable when you're happy.
谁请你们来装饰育婴室了
Who asked you to decorate the nursery?
就让我给你解释下吧  小甜心
Let me break it down for you, sweetheart.
这房子是我俩的
This is our house
我们会有一对双胞胎
and we're having twins.
谁是代孕妈妈  地下室挨着我的护士之一吗
Who's your surrogate, one of those nurses in my basement?
不...  不是的
No... no.
一个极富人性的代孕母亲  艾维拉
A very, very human surrogate, Elvira.
你可爱的母亲
Your lovely mother.
你以为你们能拐走那对双胞胎吗
You think you're gonna steal those twins?
你俩可悲的基佬
You pathetic homos couldn't steal
连自己屁眼里的屎都拐不走
the shit out of your own ass!
知道吗
You know what?
无所谓
It doesn't matter.
一旦我父母回来  我们就离开这里
As soon as my parents get back, we're leaving here.
至少他们会离开
They're leaving.
少痴心妄想了
So knock yourselves out.
亲爱的  只要你被困在这儿
Honey, your parents aren't going anywhere
你父母哪儿都去不了
as long as you're stuck here.
到时候别一把鼻涕一把泪哦  小妹妹
And don't you get all snotty, little sister.
你会求着帮我们带孩子的
You'll be begging to babysit.
这房子真大  确实会越来越寂寞
As big as this place is, it does get very, very lonely.
狠手不是不能下
It could get ugly, though.
你是剖腹产生下来的吧
Were you a C-section?
或许她肚子上有现成的伤口吧
Is there an existing zipper we might use?
注意点  你个该死的便装皇后
Watch it, you goddamn queen.
人家好怕怕哟
Oh, I am quaking in my loafers.
你打算怎办
What are you gonna do...
杀了我吗
murder me?
我的褐色贝蒂布丁20分钟后就变成黑贝蒂布丁了
My brown Betty turns to black Betty in 20 minutes.
所以有话快讲
So tell me what this is all about.
我需要帮助
I need help.
你知道在我们之前住这的那俩人吗
Do you know those two guys that lived here before us?
那对娘炮吗
Frick and Frack?
那俩怎会叫人忘记
How could I forget?
他们在楼上  而且
Well, they're upstairs and they're
他们打算绑架我妈妈的双胞胎
planning to kidnap my mother's babies
自己来抚养
and raise them themselves.
我向你保证  那是不可能发生的
Well, let me assure you that is never going to happen.
我妈妈今天就从医院回来
My mom's on her way back from the hospital today.
我不相信他们
And I don't trust them.
找你来是因为我想和那个女人谈谈
I called 'cause I want to talk to that woman,
克雷格列表上找的那个疯神婆
the Craig's List psychic.
比莉·迪恩么  要谈什么
Billie Dean? About what?
肯定会有办法摆脱这些鬼魂
Getting rid of ghosts. There must be a way.
别担心  我会解决的
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
查德  查德
Chad? Chad...?
不管你在哪  快点出来吧
Come out, come out wherever you are.
把你肮脏的爪子从床边拿开
Put your skanky claw on that crib,
不然我就让它沾满鲜血
you'll be pulling away a bloody stump.
你从哪儿找到这些东西的
Where did you find these things?
四处翻来的
Around.
前任房主们都留下的珍奇的宝藏
You'd be amazed at the little forgotten treasures left behind
会让你惊奇的
by previous occupants.
你所计划的事情是违反自然的
What you are planning to do is unnatural.
除臭剂也是违反自然的  还不是卖得很好
Deodorant's unnatural, but it's a public good.
我们会是很棒的父母
We'll make excellent parents.
男人不应该和男人在一起
Man shall not lie with man.
这有违天理
It is an abomination.
你的发型也是  不过那是你的问题了
So's that hairdo, but I figure that's your business.
你们为什么就不能安分一点  养个宠物
Why can't you people just content yourself with having pets?
为什么非要将你们扭曲的生活
Why must you subject an innocent child
强加到一个无辜的孩子身上
to your perversions?
没有任何研究显示在同性家庭中成长
There's nothing in the studies that indicates being raised
会对孩子造成负面影响
by a same-sex couple has any ill effects on children.
我想对死后的家庭也同样适用
I assume the same applies to the formerly living.
我唯一知道的研究  是血与泪的教训
Well, the only study I know is the study of blood and pain.
我的孩子是我身上掉下的肉
My children came out of my body,
这点是你永远无法理解的
and that is something that you will never be able to understand.
女士  他们只是从你的肚子里爬出来罢了
Lady, just because you happen to be the hole they crawled out of
根本毫无意义
doesn't mean a goddamn thing.
这意义非凡
It means everything.
好吧  当然了
Right. Sure.
这就是为什么每次我在自己房子里溜达时
That's why I can't even walk through my own home
总能撞见几个你那些死掉的子女
without tripping over one of your dead offspring.
我深爱我的孩子
I loved my children.
爱到死
To death.
他们都是我的一部分
They are a part of me,
那个未降生的孩子也是一样
just like that unborn child is a part of me,
我绝不会让你的脏手碰到我孙子一下
and I will not have you put your filthy hands on my grandchild.
孙子
Grandchild?
等一下
Wait a minute.
你不会是说那位小诺曼·贝茨
Are you telling me that Norman Bates Jr.
就要当爸爸了吧
is the baby daddy?
你一定会爱上这栋房子
You gotta love this house.
听我说
Listen to me.
你可以抱走另外一个
You can have the other one.
哈蒙医生的那个骨肉
The one fathered by Dr. Harmon.
他可是个迷人的男人
I mean, he's an attractive man.
但你不能抢走我孙子
But not my grandbaby.
一个金发一个黑发  就像我和帕特一样
A blond and a brunette-- just like me and Pat.
太完美了
It's perfect.
不
No.
我们两个都要定了
We definitely need both.
你这个贱人
God, you're vile.
你根本不懂得抚养孩子
You're not suited to raise children.
抚养他们
Raise them?
亲爱的  不 不
Oh, honey, no, no, no.
我们会等他们长到完美可爱的年龄
We're going to wait until they reach that perfect, adorable age--
大概一岁或一岁半左右
around a year, year and a half or so--
再用低致敏性的枕头把他们闷死
and then we're going to smother them with hypoallergenic pillows.
这样他们就会永远可爱下去了
That way, they'll be cute forever.
这里有太多的痛苦
So much pain here.
太多的留恋和遗憾
So much longing and regret.
恐惧
Fear.
悲伤
Sadness.
罪孽
Guilt.
还有扭曲
And perversion.
你现在可以帮我们找到那些鬼魂吗
Now, can you ferret out the fairies for us?
这是我们眼下最大的困扰
I mean, that's our main concern at the moment.
追踪某一个灵魂是非常难的
Targeting a particular spirit is going to be difficult.
这房子都快满员了
This is a very crowded house.
你还这么年轻
You were so young.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
天呐
Oh, God.
求你千万别说出去
Please don't tell.
不能让爸妈知道
They can't know.
我们该怎么做
So what can we do?
我们要想办法把他们与
Somehow, we have to try and dislodge them
这里的磁性吸引力分离
from the paramagnetic grip of this place.
什么东西
The what?
恶魔之力
The evil.
和其他力量没有区别  瓦奥莱特
It's a force just like any other, Violet.
就是单纯的物理学
Pure physics.
真实而强大
Real and powerful.
因各类事件产生
Created by events.
那些将灵魂的能量释放至
Events that unleash psychic energy
能够吸收灵力的环境中的事件
into the environment, where it's absorbed.
就像电池充电一样
Like the way a battery stores energy.
它随处可见
You'll see it all the time
在监狱或避难所之类的地方
in places like prisons or asylums.
负面的能量靠创伤和痛苦滋生
Negative energy feeds on trauma and pain.
将伤痛汇聚丛生
It draws those things to it.
这座房子里的力
The force here in this house
比许多人的伤痛加在一起还要巨大
is larger than the many individual traumas.
而且它有强大的欲望
And it has a need.
它想要挣脱束缚
It wants to break through.
它想要闯入我们的世界
It wants to move in our world.
它把那些被困在阴阳两界的灵魂当做通道
It's using those trapped between this world and the next as conduits.
很有趣
That's very interesting.
可是我们该拿那对同性恋怎么办
But what do we do about the gays?
怎么除掉他们
I mean, how do we get rid of them?
可能会有办法
Oh, there might be a way.
我不能保证
I can't promise...
他不可以在场
He can't be here.
泰特
Tate.
比莉·迪恩
Billie Dean,
那是我儿子
that's my boy.
他就是泰特
That's Tate.
我想帮忙
I want to help.
你已经帮得够多了
You've helped enough.
现在不行  泰特
Not now, Tate.
继续吧
Go on.
刚才是怎么回事
What was that about?
只是有时  当灵媒如此直接的面对鬼魂
It's just that, sometimes, when a medium meets a spirit so directly,
会有很强烈的反应
it has a powerful effect.
仅此而已
That's all.
你没什么可担心的
It's nothing to concern yourself about.
好了  那我们可以做些什么
Okay, so what can we do?
瓦奥莱特怎么没来
Why didn't Violet come?
瓦奥莱特最近状态不好
Violet's been having a very rough time.
她一次都没来看过我  本
She didn't come visit me once, Ben.
我是迈凯西医生  这里的住院医师
I'm Dr. Marchesi, the resident physician.
你还好吗  维维安
How are you, Vivien?
我很好  准备好回家了
Fine. Ready to go home.
你有没有说服你妻子
Have you had any luck convincing your wife
将旅行推迟到生产后
to push off the trip until after the birth?
迈凯西医生建议我卧床休息
Dr. Marchesi is recommending bed rest
因为双胞胎的缘故
because of the twins,
我完全赞同
which I wholeheartedly agree with.
我告诉他我们可以在机场找一个轮椅
And I said to him that we would get a wheelchair at the airport.
我会一直坐着到佛罗里达
I will be sitting the whole way to Florida.
我现在才怀孕六个月
And I'm only six months pregnant,
旅行没什么问题  我不会有事
so it's still okay to travel. I'll be fine.
好吧  坐轮椅是可以
All right, well, wheelchairs are all well and good,
但就像我告诉你妻子的
but as I told your wife,
我估计你的妇产医生并没有
I wouldn't be surprised if your obstetrician
建议你要采取紧急剖腹产吧
didn't recommend an immediate emergency C-section.
再有24个小时
Well, in 24 hours,
我就会在我妹妹和她家人的照顾之中
I will be in the capable hands of my sister and her family
还会有一个出色的妇产医生
and an excellent obstetrician.
我会和我所信任的人在一起
I'll be with people who I trust,
离开这座城市
and out of this city.
感谢您把这些东西拿来
Thank you for bringing these.
我会交给医生的
I'll bring them to the doctor.
我想听医生说说你的情况
I'd like to hear it from the doctor.
紧急剖腹产是吗
Emergency C-section?
我想你知道这两个孩子
I'm sure you're aware that these babies--
应该说  其中一个孩子
well, rather, one of these babies--
一直长得很快
has been developing at a rapid rate.
直到他
I mean, to the point
分离出母体  能靠自己存活
where he's ready to come out and live on his own.
与此同时  另一个孩子却日渐孱弱
And the other one seems to be getting weaker.
有时称其为宫内生食胎
Sometimes referred to as intrauterine omophagia.
所有必须的营养物质
All the necessary nutrients
都被较大的胎儿所吸收
are being devoured by the larger fetus.
可称之为阿尔法胎儿
The alpha, if you will.
你什么时候才要告诉我呢  维维安
When were you going to tell me this, Vivien?
等我们到了弗罗里达就一五一十告诉你
We will address it all when we get to Florida.
我还有事情
Well, I'm on record.
很高兴认识你们  哈蒙医生  维维安
It was nice to meet you, Dr. Harmon, Vivien.
如果我是你  我会去看一下
If I were you, I would start checking to see
那次航班上有没有医生
if there's a medical doctor on that flight.
走吧
Let's go.
驱除鬼魂是很困难的
It's difficult to banish a spirit,
不过亦非毫无可能
but not impossible.
就我所知  最成功的一次
The most successful attempt that I know of
发生在美国还被称为新大陆的时候
happened when America was known as the New World.
真的假的
Are you kidding?
那可是五百年前的事了
That's like 500 years ago.
灵魂既不遵循我们的自然法则
Spirits do not follow our physical laws.
也不受时间的影响
Nor are they affected by time.
他们唯一跟活人一样的
About the only thing they have in common
就是他们所承受的苦难
with the living is their suffering.
悔恨
Regret.
痛苦
Pain.
以及孤寂
Loneliness.
1590年
In 1590,
在如今的北卡罗来纳州沿岸
on the coast of what we now know as North Carolina,
罗诺克殖民地
the entire colony of Roanoke--
一共117个男女老少
all 117 men, women and children--
一夜之间死光了
died inexplicably.
后来那里被称为鬼地
It became known as the Ghost Colony
就是因为那些怨灵还在那游荡
because the spirits remained.
他们常出没于住在附近的土著部落
They haunted the native tribes living in the surrounding area.
滥杀无辜
Killing indiscriminately.
那位长老知道他必须有所行动
The elder knew he had to act.
于是他施了一个驱逐咒
He cast a banishment curse.
首先  他收集了一些
First, he collected the personal belongings
死去殖民的贴身物品
of all the dead colonists.
然后烧了它们
Then they burned them.
鬼魂受到护身符的召唤而现形
The ghosts appeared, summoned by their talismans.
但就在那些幽灵造成进一步伤害之前
But before the spirits could cause them any more harm,
那位长老完成了诅咒
the elder completed the curse
可以永远驱逐这些鬼魂
that would banish the ghosts forever.
怎么驱逐
How?
就念一个词
By uttering a single word.
他们发现刻在殖民地的
The same word found carved on a post
圆锥桩子上的那个词
at the aband coned colony.
克柔投安
Croatoan.
现在你知道自己该做什么了
So now you know what you have to do.
她都说了些什么
What did she say?
我们得找些他的东西来
We have to get something of his.
重要物品
Something important.
比如说传家宝或者婚戒什么的
Like an heirloom or a ring.
就像护身符一样的东西
Like a talisman.
如果我们拿到了他的护身符然后进行驱魔
If we have the talisman and we do this special ritual,
他就会消失了
he'll be gone.
听起来就是胡扯
That sounds like bullshit.
比莉·迪恩不是骗子  她专业驱鬼的
Billie Dean's for real. She studies this stuff.
壮点的那家伙  他带着戒指
The bigger guy, he wears a ring.
跟婚戒差不多  但我记不清
It's like a wedding ring, but I can't remember
-到底戴在哪只手上了  -我不信任她
- which hand it's on. - I don't trust her!
她那么说我是为什么
Now, why'd she say all that stuff about me?
我干坏事了是吗
I did something bad, didn't I?
我们去找戒指吧
Let's just get the ring.
怎么能行得通呢
How does it work?
孩子将来是都叫你俩爸爸呢
Will the kid call you both daddy,
还是一个叫妈妈呢
or is one of you the mom?
我只是来捣乱的
I'm just messing with you.
不过说真的
Seriously, though,
你真的准备好这些了吗
are you ready for all this?
你在我印象里可不是什么换尿布
I mean, you never struck me as the diapers
还有半夜喂奶的形象
and midnight feedings type.
或许在你用火钳捅我屁股之前
Maybe you should have taken a few minutes to get to know me
该花几分钟了解一下我的
before you stuck a fireplace poker up my ass.
有道理
Fair enough.
我们会在这里相处很长一段时间
We're all going to be here for a long time, so...
或许我们该想个办法忘记旧账既往不咎
maybe we can figure out a way to let bygones be bygones
然后和平共处
and, you know, cohabitate.
是你杀了我
I'm dead because of you!
我总有能帮上忙的地方吧
Well, there's got to be something I could offer you.
就因为我们已经死了
I mean, just because we're dead
不代表我们没有需求
doesn't mean we don't have wants.
没有欲望
Desires.
婚姻貌似很艰难
Marriage looks hard.
特别是跟那家伙结婚
Especially to that guy.
总是对你颐指气使
Always on you all the time.
却从不考虑你想要什么  对吗
And never in the ways you want, right?
要等到
It must suck
每年的万圣节才能来点不寻常的刺激
to have to wait till Halloween every year
肯定感觉很糟吧
to get a little strange.
我杀不了你
I can't kill you,
但我可以让你遭罪
but I can make you suffer!
最棒的是  等我揍完了
Best part is, when I'm done,
你很快就会痊愈
you'll heal up and I can beat
而我就又可以把你打得屁滚尿流了
the shit out of you all over again!
再狠一点
Harder!
-我就喜欢粗暴  -不该是这样的
- I like it rough. - Not supposed to be like this!
我不该在这里的
I'm not supposed to be here!
看着我  看着我
Look at me. Look at me!
我本来是要离开这里的
I was going to get out!
我恋爱了  上帝保佑
I fell in love. God help me, I was going
我本是要离开这里跟他在一起的
to get out and be with him,
而你却杀了我  让我困在这里
and then you killed me, and now I'm stuck here...
跟他困在一起
with him!
查德
Chad.
我不会进这间屋子的
I won't go in the house.
你不用进去
You don't have to.
我整理了你的行李
I packed your things.
瓦奥莱特整理好了吗
Is Violet packed?
我告诉她我们要离开了
I told her we're leaving.
你还好吗
You ok?
你拿到了什么
Wh'd you get?
他把它脱下来去上漆了
He took it off to paint.
一个鬼魂怎么会需要手表呢
Why does a ghost need a watch?
瓦奥莱特
Violet!
你在我面前消失了  这是什么情况
You disappeared on me! What the hell happened?!
瓦奥莱特  你妈妈在车里等着
Violet, your mom's waiting in the car.
我们还要赶飞机
We have a plane to catch.
很好  走得越远越好
Good. Go far away.
别再把妈妈带到这间屋子里来
Just don't bring mom in the house.
-你说什么呢  你要一起走  -我不
- What are you talking about? You're coming with us. - No!
我能照顾好自己
I can take care of myself.
如果你们想的话  以后可以回来找我
And if you want to, you can come back for me later.
但现在  你们必须相信我
But for right now, you just have to trust me
赶快离开这里
and get the hell out of here.
告诉妈妈我爱她  希望她母子平安
Tell mom I love her and good luck with the babies.
你怎么回事
What's the matter with you? Huh?
嗑药了还是怎么的
Are you high or something?
我倒想
I wish.
瓦奥莱特  我红灯停车的时候你不见了
Violet, I stopped at a red light and you were gone.
-你上哪去了  -没上哪去
- Where did you go? - Nowhere.
我就在这里
I was right here.
我也想去的
I wanted to come.
我发誓
I swear.
我无法离开这房子
I couldn't leave the house.
够了  你在说谎
Stop it! You're lying.
你肯定嗑药了  我能看出来
You're on drugs, I can tell.
告诉我  是什么药
Tell me what kind, right now.
快说
Tell me!
我已经死了
I'm dead!
你怎么还不明白
Don't you get it?
死在这所房子里的人  根本无法离开
When you die in this house, you don't get to leave.
所以你需要赶紧离开
That's why you need to go,
把妈妈送到安全的地方
and take Mom somewhere safe.
-我正打算如此  -本
- That's exactly what I'm gonna do. - Ben!
你得和我一起离开
You're coming with me.
维维安
Vivien!
维维安  是...孩子要出生了吗
Oh, Vivien, is-is the baby coming?
不
No!
不  不会这么早
No, it's too soon!
不  不  不
No, no, no!
不会的  亲爱的
No, honey.
如果孩子想出世  只能顺其自然
When a child is ready to be born, there's no stopping it.
-不  -快点  得把你抬到屋内
- No! - Come on, we got to get you to the house.
不
No!
我服了一些药
I took some pills.
并非存心想自杀
I didn't mean to kill myself.
本
Ben!
怎么了
What's wrong?!
孩子要出生了
The babies are coming.
不  不
No! No!
不
No!
放松
Take it easy, now.
记住要呼吸  呼气吸气
Don't forget to breathe. Breathe.
没信号
I can't get any service.
我得去医院
I got to go to the hospital now!
来不及了  已经能看到胎头了
It's too late for that; you're already crowning.
我去联系豪尔医生
I'm gonna call Dr. Hall.
让他们赶紧派辆救护车
We'll get you an ambulance right away.
呼气吸气  维维安  呼气吸气
Breathe, Vivien, breathe.
天呐   很痛
Oh, God! It hurts.
痛苦是难免的  亲爱的
Well, of course it does, honey.
女人就苦在这儿
That's a woman's curse.
她不能在这分娩
She can't give birth here.
不安全
It's not safe.
那就保护好她  你知道该怎么做
Well, then make it safe. You know what to do.
该死
Damn it.
我操
Shit!
给我滚开
Get away from there!
你们几个兔崽子快滚开
You kids get away from there!
哈蒙医生
Dr. Harmon.
是时候了
It's time.
护士  把我的医护包拿过来
Nurse, bring me my doctor bag.
这不对头
This is wrong.
给我找12号手术刀
Find me the 12-gauge scalpel.
我们得带你离开这儿
We have to get you out of here.
毛巾怎么还没来
Where are those towels?
铺在她身下
Spread them out underneath her.
这房子
This house.
This house!
本
Ben?!
醒醒
Wake up.
这所房子正竭尽全力帮你
This house is trying to help.
此刻不容你拒绝
And right now, you are in no position to refuse.
你的妻子需要你
Your wife needs you.
你最好振作些  赶紧过去
So you better pull yourself together and get in there.
照顾好她
For her.
本
Ben?!
这些都是什么人
Who are all these people?
Who are these people?!
没事的  宝贝儿
It's okay, baby.
他们是来帮我们的
They're here to help us.
我都忘了分娩有多痛
I forgot how painful this is.
你有什么镇痛药吗  医生
Do you have a little something for her, Doctor?
乙醚
Ether.
缓和一下
Just to take the edge off.
救命
Help.
我感觉又要开始了
Oh, I feel another one coming.
亲爱的  记住要呼吸
Okay, honey, remember your breathing.
你做得很好  你做得很好
You're doing great. You're doing great.
坚持住  亲爱的
Just hang in there, honey.
你做得很好
You're doing great.
好了  再用力一次
Here we go. One more push.
放松呼吸  亲爱的
Just breathe, honey.
呼气吸气  记住要呼气吸气
Breathe. Remember your breathing.
呼气吸气
Breathe.
-呼气吸气  -我恨你
- Breathe. - I hate you.
我爱你
I love you.
用力  用力  用力  再来一次
Push, push, push! One more!
再用力一次
Here we go. One more push.
再使劲儿一次
One more big push.
她要出来了  加油  用力
Here she comes. Come on, push!
加油  亲爱的  用力
Come on, honey, push!
用力  用力  亲爱的
Push! Push, honey!
我爱你
God, I love you.
呼气吸气
Breathe.
我不想失去你
I never wanted to lose you.
永远都不会的
You never will.
她要出来了
She's coming!
-加油  用力  -她出来了
- Come on! Push! - Here she comes!
用力
Push!
加油  亲爱的
Come on, honey!
用力
Push!
是个健康的小闺女
It's a healthy baby girl.
爸爸要过来切断脐带吗
Daddy, you want to cut the cord?
天呐
Oh, my God.
上帝啊
瓦奥莱特
Violet.
这个孩子胎死腹中
Your baby is stillborn.
是男孩还是女孩
Is it a boy or a girl?
我能抱抱吗
Can I hold it?
不行
No.
还不行  亲爱的
Not just yet, sweetheart.
还有一个
You've got another one coming.
你到底在做什么  小姐
What exactly do you think you're doing, young lady?
我那一万二的名表是不是被你扔进火炉了
Is that my $12,000 watch that you're putting into the furnace?
克柔投安
Croatoan!
开个玩笑
Just kidding.
谁给你出的这主意
So where'd you get that one?
是之前来过的那位连指甲都是假的灵媒吗
That press-on nail psychic who was here earlier?
不会吧  这你都信
I mean, really?
罗诺克咒语
The Roanoke spell?
我宁愿你
Please, tell me you'll be
切个鸡喉什么的
slitting the throat of a chicken next,
绝对能震撼到我
because I've always found that very dramatic.
详见本季第一集
你们之前烧鼠尾草净灵那招
I also quite enjoy the burning of the sage
也让我相当之雀跃
to rid the house of spirits.
-没用  -当然没用
- It didn't work. - Of course it didn't work.
纯粹瞎扯淡
It's bullshit.
完全是瞎扯
It's all bullshit.
人们杜撰这些咒语和圣歌
People make up these spells and chants
不过是为了营造一切都在掌控之中的幻觉
in order to feel like they're in control.
事实是
Well, guess what?
他们无法掌控
They're not.
也从未掌控过
Never have been.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我自个儿的瞎扯淡仪式
My own bullshit ritual.
不会有什么育儿室
There's not gonna be any nursery.
我们也不会当父母
We're not gonna be parents.
你母亲的孩子将安然无恙
Your mother's babies are safe.
至少不会受到我们的伤害
From us, at least.
我注定要和一个不爱我的男人
I'm doomed to spend eternity
度过永生
with a man who doesn't love me.
当然  我这还不是最糟糕的
Of course, it could be worse.
你的男人虽然爱你...
Your man does love you...
可他永远都会是个怪物
but he'll always be a monster.
你错了
You're wrong.
泰特已经改过自新
Tate's changed.
他甚至都不记得曾经做过什么
He doesn't even remember what he did.
他什么时候改的
When did he change?
谋杀我之时吗
When he murdered me?
还是在他杀了我男友之时
When he murdered my boyfriend?
或者  是在他强奸了你母亲之后改变的
Or did he change when he raped your mother?
你说什么
What?
不  你在说谎
No, that's a lie.
是吗
Is it?
我想你就要发现真相了
I think you're about to find out.
维维安  吸气  你得吸气
Vivien, breathe. You have to breathe.
维维安  吸气呼气
Vivien, breathe!
你得深呼吸
You have to breathe!
-我现在要用钳子了  -怎么了
- I need forceps, now. - What's happening?
她难产了
It's dystocia.
耻骨联合
骨盆前方两片骨头间靠韧带及纤维软骨组织联接起来的区域
我得从耻骨联合处把孩子夹出来
I have to manilate the baby through the pubic symphysis.
不行了  本
I can't, Ben.
我不行了
I can't do it.
你可以的
You can do it.
我保证  看着我
I-I promise you. Look at me.
你可以做到的
You can do this.
哈蒙医生  等我说可以时再让你妻子用力
Dr. Harmon, have your wife stop pushing until I say so.
维维安  听得见我说话吗
Vivien, can you hear me?
我说用力时  你再用力
You have to stop pushing until I tell you.
我快痛死了
It hurts so much!
用你最大的力气抓我的手  握紧
Squeeze my hand as hard as you can! Squeeze!
准备纱布止血
Get the gauze ready to stop the bleeding.
-就现在  哈蒙医生  -用力  维维安
- Now, Dr. Harmon. - Push, Vivien!
你得用力  用力
You have to push! Push!
用力  用力
Push! Push!
孩子要出来了
He's coming.
使劲  你做的很棒  小维
Push! You're doing great, Viv!
你做的很棒  小维
You're doing great, Viv.
天啊  我要被撕裂了
Oh, God, it's ripping me apart!
别停下  亲爱的
Don't stop, angel!
就快结束了  我看见他了
The end is in sight. I can see him.
你成功了  宝贝
You did it, babe.
亲爱的  你成功了
Honey, you did it.
成功了
You did it.
-一切还好吗  -她在流血
- Is everything all right? - She's bleeding.
我得先止血
I have to stop the bleeding.
把脐带剪了  该分开母亲和孩子了
Cut the cord. It's time to separate mother and son.
我能看下孩子吗
Can I see the baby?
把他给我
Hand him to me.
我先为他擦洗下  马上就带回来
I'll get him washed up. I'll bring him right back.
医生  一切都还好吗
Doctor, is everything all right?
你是不是有毛病
Oh, what is the matter with you?
他是我见过最漂亮的婴儿
He's the most beautiful baby I've ever seen.
鲜血和痛苦造就了孩子的完美
From blood and pain come perfection.
婊子们
Hey, bitches.
我孩子身上的黏液  你们弄干净了吗
You get all that slime off my baby yet?
护士  用力压住这里
Nurse, I need pressure on this.
到底是怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
她快要休克了  我止不住大出血
She's going into shock. I can't stop the hemorrhaging.
维维安  别离开我
Vivien, stay with me.
维维安
Vivien.
妈妈
Mom...
瓦奥莱特
Violet.
很抱歉我没去医院看望你
I'm sorry I didn't go see you at the hospital.
我想去  但我不能够去
I wanted to, but I couldn't.
可现在你在啊  这才是最关键的
You're here now-- that's all that matters.
维维安
Vivien.
听我说
Listen to me.
留心听我的话
Concentrate on my words.
我们会幸福的  亲爱的
We can be happy, honey.
就像以前一样幸福
Just like we were before.
就像在我出轨之前
Before my mistakes,
搬进这屋子之前一样幸福
before this house.
没事的  妈妈
It's okay, Mom.
如果你感到痛苦
If you're in pain,
就随它去吧
let go.
看来我别无选择了
I don't think I have a choice.
坚持住  维维安  别离开我
Hold on, Vivien. Stay with me.
来我这边吧
Come to this side.
就随它去吧
Let go.
你可以和我在一起
You can be with me.
不要死
Don't die.
不准给我死  维维安
Don't die on me, Vivien.
我们仍要共度一生
We can still have a life together.
我们仍会幸福的
We can still be happy.
我妈妈死了
My mom is dead.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我知道你们母女很亲近
I know you were close.
是的  我们很亲
Yeah, we were.
现在就剩我爸孤零零地在楼下了
My dad's down there all alone now.
我很难过
That makes me sad.
我喜欢你爸爸
I like your dad.
他对我很好
He was nice to me.
他对所有的病人都很好
He's nice to all his patients.
-甚至是那些对他撒谎的病人  -什么
- Even the ones who lie to him. - What?
当初为什么要请他帮你看病
Why did you start seeing him in the first place?
康丝坦斯觉得你需要帮助
Constance thought you needed help.
是的  我确实需要
I did. I do.
你知道自己已经死了
You knew you were dead.
是的
Yeah.
我知道
I knew.
知道是怎么死的吗
Do you know why?
警察开枪打死了我
The cops shot me.
就在这里  在这间房里
Right here in this room.
为什么  为什么他们要开枪打你
Why? Why did they shoot you?
我不知道
I don't know.
因为你杀了人  泰特
You murdered people, Tate.
杀了像我们这样的孩子
Kids. Like us.
就是万圣节那晚来找我们的孩子
The kids that came to us on Halloween.
我为什么要这么做
Why would I do that?
不可能  我为什么要这么做
No... Why would I do that?
我不知道
I don't know.
为什么你杀了先前住在这里的那俩家伙
Why'd you kill those guys who lived here before us?
为什么你要强奸我妈妈
Why would you rape my mother?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
后来我就变了
I was different then.
我曾以为你和我一样
I used to think you were like me.
是被罪恶的事物所吸引
You were attracted to the darkness,
但  泰特  你就是罪恶的化身
but, Tate, you are the darkness.
不是的  只是在遇见你之前
No. Before you,
我是这样的
that's all there was.
你是照进我世界唯一的光亮
You're the only light I've ever known.
你改变了我  瓦奥莱特
You've changed me, Violet.
我相信
I believe that.
我爱你  泰特
I love you, Tate.
但我不能原谅你
But I can't forgive you.
你得为你所做的事付出代价
You have to pay for what you did.
为所有你造成的痛苦
All the pain you caused.
为所有的悲痛
All the sorrow.
是你杀了我妈妈
You murdered my mother.
-不是我  -就是
- No! - You did!
不管它是婴儿还是别的什么
That baby-- whatever it was--
就是它害死了她
it killed her.
我不能和你在一起
I can't be with you.
我也不会和你在一起
I won't be with you.
你在说什么
What are you saying?
我说走开
I'm saying go away.
什么
What?
不不  别这么做
No, no, don't do this.
走开  泰特
Go away, Tate.
我只想要你  我只剩下你了
You're all I want! You're all I have!
走开
Go away!
你刚才可真勇敢
That was very brave.
我为你感到骄傲
I'm proud of you.
妈妈
Mom...
对不起  妈妈
I'm sorry, Mom.
很抱歉你也死了
I'm sorry you had to die.
很抱歉你失去了孩子
I'm sorry you lost your baby.
可我并没有失去你这个孩子啊
But I didn't lose my baby.